Summertime Sadness
夏末的忧伤
压制:随Feng
歌手：Lana Del Rey
I got my red dress on tonight
今晚我穿上火红的舞裙
Dancin' in the dark in the pale moonlight
在黑暗中与那惨白的月光共舞
Done my hair up real big,beauty queen style
还有我那如选美王后般华丽的发型
High heels off,I'm feelin' alive
脱下高跟鞋 我感受着活力
Oh my god,I feel it in the air
哦 上帝 爱的感觉弥漫在空气中
Telephone wires above,Are sizzlin' like a snare
电话那头嘶嘶作响 如同你凝视我一般
Honey I'm on fire,I feel it everywhere
亲爱的 我感到每个角落的热情都在燃烧着我
Nothing scares me anymore
我无所畏惧
Kiss me hard before you go
在你临走之前请用力亲吻我
Summertime sadness
纪念这夏末的忧伤
I just wanted you to know
只想让你知道
That baby,you the best
亲爱的 你对我来说是最优秀的
I've got that summertime,summertime sadness
这夏日的忧郁啊
Su-su-summertime,summertime sadness
这夏日的忧郁在不停蔓延
Got that summertime,summertime sadness
啊 夏日的忧郁
I've got that summertime,I've got that summertime
这夏日的忧郁啊 这夏日的忧郁啊
Got that summertime,I've got that summertime
啊 夏日的忧郁
I've got that summertime
这夏日的忧郁啊
Summertime sadness
纪念这夏末的忧伤
I'm feelin' electric tonight
今晚我的感觉像触电一样
Cruisin' down the coast,goin' about 99
乘着99号的游轮
Got my bad baby by my heavenly side
有你的地方便是天堂
I know if I go,I'll die happy tonight
就算我离开了 这也是最快乐的夜晚
Oh my god,I feel it in the air
哦 上帝 爱的感觉弥漫在空气中
Telephone wires above,Are sizzlin' like a snare
电话那头嘶嘶作响 如同你凝视我一般
Honey I'm on fire,I feel it everywhere
亲爱的 我感到每个角落的热情都在燃烧着我
Nothing scares me anymore
我无所畏惧
Kiss me hard before you go
在你临走之前请努力亲吻我
Summertime sadness
纪念这夏末的忧伤
I just wanted you to know
只想让你知道
That baby,you the best
亲爱的 你对我来说是最优秀的
I've got that summertime,summertime sadness
这夏日的忧郁啊
Su-su-summertime,summertime sadness
这夏日的忧郁不停在蔓延
Got that summertime,summertime sadness
啊 夏日的忧郁
Oh, oh oh
哦 哦 哦
I've got that summertime,I've got that summertime
这夏日的忧郁啊
Su-su-summertime,Su-su-summertime
夏日
I've got that summertime,I've got that summertime
这夏日的忧郁啊
Summertime sadness
纪念这夏末的忧伤
Got that summertime,I've got that summertime
这夏日的忧郁啊
Summertime sadness
纪念这夏末的忧伤
Su-su-summertime,summertime sadness
这夏日的忧郁不停在蔓延
压制:随Feng